<resources>
    <string name="app_name">COEP Clubs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_boat_club">BoatClub</string>
    <string name="boatinfo">COEP is proud to have a Boat Club, which is one of its kind in the country. Situated on the banks of Mula River, this club was established in the year 1928. The club owns about 70 trainee and racing boats, which can be used for various competitions besides regular practice. The club is an active member of professional associations like Maharashtra Rowing Association (MRA) and the Amateur Rowers Association (ARAE).It has wide range of unique boats that include punts, single sculls, racing pair, racing four, racing eight, Jr. Whiff, Sr. Whiff, training scull, tuff four, canoes and kayaks. In addition to that boat club also houses a well equipped gymnasium. This includes a sprawling indoor hall comprising of four badminton courts and one table-tennis court, thus providing students of this college with best athletic endeavors. It hosts a canteen as well. Membership of the Boat club is mandatory to all the under graduate and postgraduate students seeking admission in this institute. Moreover, facilities of the boat club are extended to every Alumni of this College.The Boatclub, as it is known, is one of the favourite spot for most people in college. The riverside ambience offers a majestic view of the Mula River. The Boatclub has become synonymous with COEP for every COEPian.</string>
    <string name="m">Motto</string>
    <string name="boatmotto">Row To Win</string>
    <string name="a">About</string>
    <string name="achieve">Achievements</string>
    <string name="fmi">For More Info</string>
    <string name="con">Contact</string>
    <string name="boatcontact">Boat CLub Secretary</string>
    <string name="astroinfo">Who hasn’t marveled at the celestial wonders and experienced a sense of awe at being a part of such an infinite expanse? Since its foundation in 2004, the CoEP Astronomy club seeks to build on this fascination and brings innovation and passion to its vision of spreading the awareness and knowledge of astronomy and space sciences to the students. The CoEP Astronomy club, an ambitious team driven by amateur astronomers, has managed to conjure up a lot of interest amongst students in the science of stargazing. Integrating technical skill with astronomical science, the club has initiated many projects, some of which being the construction of one of India’s largest amateur built telescope – a 12” Newtonian reflector, construction of mobile, inflatable planetarium dome, etc. The club strives to quench a student’s thirst for astronomy by organizing various exciting events such as Star Party (a fun-filled night of star-gazing), Planetarium visits, Quiztronomy (a quiz to test people’s knowledge on everything seen beyond the night sky), Telescope building and handling sessions (telescope – every astronomers weapon), and many more. The club is also looking forward to publish its Newsletter from the academic year 2014-15 in order to promote righteous information about Astronomy and related science. In addition to this, the club in association with the Inter-University Centre for Astronomy and Astrophysics, Pune (IUCAA) organizes the event StareWay to Heaven during MindSpark with an aim to bring astronomy to the masses. Within this, a mobile planetarium is set up in the college, where the night sky is simulated and the people are introduced to various constellations and stars. Discussions and brainstorming sessions are also held every week wherein members explore the Universe.</string>
    <string name="astrocontact">Astronomy Head</string>
    <string name="pc">Project Completed</string>
    <string name="rsccontact">RSC Head</string>
    <string name="rscinfo"><![CDATA[Robot Study Circle (known as RSC) is a community of students guided by faculty members, industrial experts & alumni, who find pleasure in Robotics. It is a platform for like-minded people to come together, share knowledge and strive to create futuristic automated machines. The objective of Robot Study Circle is to build international quality Robots, that will prove to be useful in a variety of environments, especially in the industries.]]></string>
    <string name="procom">Basic Line Tracer Robot\nAutonomous Chess Playing Robot\nQuadrotor Under Water Autonomous Vehicle (Fish robot) (Won Best Mini Project Award 2011)\nFire Extinguisher Robot (Won Best Mini Project Award 2012)\nWireless Image Transmission 5-Band Graphic Equalizer Bomb Detection Disposal Squad Assisting robot\nAutonomous Rubik’s Cube solving Robot\nHydroquadrotor Can Picker Robot (Won Best Mini Project Award in 2013)</string>
    <string name="rscachieve"><![CDATA[Design & Manufacturing of Robot for Pune Police Bomb Detection & Desposal Squad Best\nIdea Award in Robocon 2014\nBest Innovative Design Award in Robocon 2013\n2nd Runner-up at ABU Asia Pacific ROBOCON 2012\n2nd Runner-up at ABU Asia Pacific ROBOCON 2011\nBest Manual Operator Award at ABU Asia Pacific ROBOCON 2011\nForbes Marshall outstanding project Award for year 2009-10 to Robot Study Circle team for Design & Development of Quad rotor\nCOEP Alumni Association’s best project Award to a team from Robot Study Circle for Design and Manufacturing of Self Balancing Personal Transportation Vehicle (Mechanical Department)\nCOEP Alumni Association’s best project Award to two teams from Robot Study Circle(E&TC Department): \nAutonomous Underwater Vehicle (First prize). \nGesture Controlled Robotic Arm (Fourth Prize).]]></string>
    <string name="op">Ongoing Projects</string>
    <string name="onpro">Wall Climbing Robot\nUnder Car Scanner\nQuadrotor Base Surveillance\nUnder water wireless communication\nHovercraft</string>
    <string name="ancinfo">ANC is one of the oldest group at college. The Arts and Crafts group, fondly called as \'AnC\' in the college, has made COEP proud by creating the Guinness World Record for the longest painting by numbers in 2008. It has members right from the first year up to the final year. All the activities of the Arts and Crafts group always have something new, creative and innovative. The Arts and Crafts group has been instrumental in decorating the entire COEP campus during college festivals like Mind Spark, Zest, Regatta and also during the annual gathering. The Arts and Crafts students organise an annual exhibition every year in the college campus where the team displays its art collection and also encourages other students to participate.</string>
    <string name="anccontact">ANC Head</string>
    <string name="photoinfo">Welcome to official Photography Club of Govt.College Of Engineering,Pune (COEP). The Club consists of Amateur Photographers who have come together to share and help eachother to learn the art of Photography, and Undertake Photography as an Interesting Hobby. The club will initiate conducting photo-walks, various workshops and learning sessions on photography as well as post-processing.</string>
    <string name="photocontact">Photography Club Head</string>
    <string name="danceinfo">COEP Dance Club is an organization that allows it members to experience the wonder of dance and the joy of performing. Students are exposed to different styles of dance from ballet to theater, modern, hip hop, tap and jazz. They learn to see dance as an art, a way of expression. Sometimes it is just the simple expression of fun and joy and other times there is a poignant message to be relayed. Dance Club allows even the non-dancer to be part of the excitement of the performance. Everyone in Dance club participates in the wonder of the annual show.We invite you all for a journey filled with endless dance and fun.Keep Dancing!</string>
    <string name="dancecontact">Dance Club Head</string>
    <string name="neminfo">Nemesis is a team from College of Engineering, Pune working under CoEP Motorsports, that participate at the annually held BAJA SAE.</string>
    <string name="nemcontact">Team Nemesis Head</string>
    <string name="nemachieve">2007 \n1st Overall Winners\n\n   2008\n  2nd in Design\n\n   2012 \n 1st in Acceleration\n\n   2012 South Africa\n  1st Cost Report \n 2nd Feasibility of Mass Production \n 2nd Skidpad  \n2nd Design\n  6th Endurance\n  6th Overall  \n\n 2013 \n 1st in CAE \n 1st in Build Quality \n 1st in Acceleration \n 1st in Raftar (Quickest Lap)\n  1st in Endurance Race\n  1st Overall Winners \n \n 2013 South Africa \n 1st Cost Report \n 3rd Design \n 1st Endurance \n 3rd Overall \n\n  2014 India  \n1st CAE \n 1st Acceleration \n 1st Manuverability \n 2nd Hill climb \n 2nd Suspension and traction \n 2nd Raftaar\n  2nd Build quality\n  2nd Overall Champions \n \n 2015 India \n 1st Overall Champions \n 1st Acceleration\n  1st Hill Climb \n 1st Raftaar \n 2nd CAE award \n 2nd Build quality \n 2nd Safe Vehicle Award \n 2nd Innovation \n\n  2015 Maryland USA \n 6th Design \n 12th Suspension\n  13th Hill Climb\n  19th Endurance \n 15th Overall Performance\n  \n 2016 India\n  1st - Overall Champions\n  1st - Acceleration\n  1st - Suspension and Traction\n  1st - Engineering Design\n  1st - Technology Innovation\n  2nd - Maneuverability\n  2nd - Raftar\n  2nd - CAE\n  2nd - Build Quality\n  2nd - Safest Vehicle\n  Special Award - Best Driver\n \n   2016 Tennessee USA\n  3rd Design\n  9th Overall Performance</string>
    <string name="suninfo">Team COEP Sunrisers Is established at College of Engineering Pune with the aim of designing, fabricating, testing and racing a solar-electric vehicle.</string>
    <string name="suncontact">Sunrisers Head</string>
    <string name="octinfo">Team Octane Racing, from COEP, is a group of dedicated automobile engineers ought to make best racing car on the track for competitions as SUPRA and FSI.</string>
    <string name="octcontact">Octane Racing Head</string>
    <string name="octachieve">1st Engineering Design at SUPRA SAE-INDIA 2015\n  1st Autocross And Most Promising Team award at Formula Student India, 2015 \n 2nd Best Overall Award, 2014 \n Computer Aided Engineering Award 2011</string>
    <string name="aeroinfo"><![CDATA[This is COEP\'s exclusive Aero Modelling club. It is an inter-disciplinary student activity. The club is established with the aim of producing awareness about the booming field of Aeronautics. The club activity mainly consists of building remote controlled aeroplanes & fly them. The planes built by the club members are officially entered into technical festivals of prestigious institutes in the country. The club also organizes guest lectures relevant to the field. At present, there are about 20 members in the club.]]></string>
    <string name="aircontact">Aero Zealous Head</string>
    <string name="bcquizmotto">Ignorance is the curse of God; knowledge is the wing wherewith we fly to heaven.</string>
    <string name="bcqinfo">Knowledge is at the forefront of every activity we undertake, in one way or the other. Man has an unending thirst to know more. This thirst is the directly the engine that drives all progress in any field. From the time that the wooden club was the smartest thing invented, we as a race have been unyielding in the pursuit of knowledge.\n\n The Boat Club Quiz Club (BCQC) was founded in 1999 with a similar drive in our minds. The knowledge transfers occurred by that most beautiful of formats – a quiz. Enthusiasts would gather at the Boat Club on Saturday evenings and hone their quizzing talents. With an open and creative attitude, it grew to Pune-wide status. Nationally, it has a reputation for being very innovative despite its relative smaller size, and many of its members have won top Indian quizzes. CoEPians have always been at the heart of the club and the BCQC\'s continuing success is an illustration of the intellectual and creative qualities of CoEPian minds. \n\n The BCQC is an open group, which means that you could be anyone at all and belong to the club. You could be an engineering student, a medical student, an MBA aspirant, a working professional or anything you want. All you need is a genuine interest in quizzing to be a member of the BCQC. \n\nApart from gathering once a week to hold informal quiz sessions, the group now holds about 15 formal quizzes a year spanning across age groups. The largest open quiz in Pune – Chakravyuh, organized with MindSpark – also occurs under the aegis of the BCQC. The club became an official CoEP club in the year 2010. The college chapter holds several quizzes for CoEP students throughout the year on a wide variety of topics. The quizzes are anticipated by all and often take place to packed houses. </string>
    <string name="bcqjoin">The BCQC offers a lot to its members and there are a lot of reasons to join the club: \n\nQuizzing as a sport greatly enhances the inquisitiveness of students helping them explore a wide range of topics. \nIt increases daily awareness and helps boost positive habits such as reading and independent research. \nStudents are up to date in recent development across a large range of fields- the requirement of the day is to be well informed. \nIt greatly enhances their ability to sound very well-informed in discussions. \nStudents get a chance to meet people from all walks of life and exchange stories.</string>
    <string name="j">Why To Join?</string>
    <string name="bcqccontact">BC Quiz Club Head</string>
    <string name="spandanmotto">Bond with the society ... Straight from the heart</string>
    <string name="spandan_info">SPANDAN was established in 2003 by the students of COEP. It is a group of dedicated youth who work on various social activities in the areas of education, environment and healthcare. SPANDAN, as its name suggests, is the concern that originates straight from the heart of every team member towards the unprivileged section of the society. Spandan aims at creating a strong sense of social commitment among the people and with the help of them work for the betterment of the society. We need youth who wish to pay back to the society as Spandan strongly believes that if we help each other, the world will definitely be a better place to live in.</string>
    <string name="spandan_activity">Activities of Spandan</string>
    <string name="spandan_activity_info">Team Spandan arranges Blood Donation Camps in college campus. On the day of Rakshabandhan, the team visits an orphanage. There are events like environment friendly idol immersion during Ganpati Festival, Blind School Visit to motivate the students through various activities. The team also organizes a two day Village Camp for the rural youth as well as villagers through activities focused on education, recreation and social awareness. Diwali products which are made by the blind students are distributed to our faculty on no profit no loss basis. There is also a continuous teaching activity carried out by team members.</string>
    <string name="why_to_join">What would the members gain from joining the team?</string>
    <string name="why_to_join_info">· Strong sense of social responsibility\n
                                    · Improve management abilities and teamwork\n
                                    · Provide platform to enhance leadership skills\n
                                    · Work for the betterment of the society</string>
    <string name="motto_tedx">Be The Change</string>
    <string name="tedx_about">TED is a nonprofit devoted to spreading ideas, usually in the form of short, powerful talks (18 minutes or less). TED began in 1984 as a conference where Technology, Entertainment and Design converged, and today covers almost all topics — from science to business to global issues — in more than 100 languages. Meanwhile, independently run TEDx events help share ideas in communities around the world.</string>
    <string name="tedx_mission">Our Mission: Spread ideas</string>
    <string name="tedx_mission_info">TED is a global community, welcoming people from every discipline and culture who seek a deeper understanding of the world. We believe passionately in the power of ideas to change attitudes, lives and, ultimately, the world. On TED.com, we\'re building a clearinghouse of free knowledge from the world\'s most inspired thinkers — and a community of curious souls to engage with ideas and each other, both online and at TED and TEDx events around the world, all year long. In fact, everything we do — from our Conferences to our TED Talks to the projects sparked by the TED Prize, from the global TEDx community to the TED-Ed lesson series — is driven by this goal: How can we best spread great ideas? TED is owned by a nonprofit, nonpartisan foundation. Our agenda is to make great ideas accessible and spark conversation.</string>
    <string name="history_tedx">History</string>
    <string name="history_ted_info">TED was born in 1984 out of Richard Saul Wurman\'s observation of a powerful convergence among three fields: technology, entertainment and design. The first TED included a demo of the compact disc, the e-book and cutting-edge 3D graphics from Lucasfilm, while mathematician Benoit Mandelbrot demonstrated how to map coastlines using his developing theory of fractal geometry. But despite a stellar lineup, the event lost money, and it was six years before Wurman and partner Harry Marks tried again. This time, in 1990, the world was ready and the numbers worked. The TED Conference became an annual event in Monterey, California, attracting a growing and influential audience from many different disciplines united by their curiosity and open-mindedness – and also by their shared discovery of an exciting secret. (Back then, TED was an invitation-only event.) TED Talk: Chris Anderson shares his vision for TED Meanwhile the roster of presenters broadened to include scientists, philosophers, musicians, business and religious leaders, philanthropists and many others. For many attendees, TED became one of the intellectual and emotional highlights of the year. That was certainly true for media entrepreneur Chris Anderson, who met with Wurman in 2000 to discuss the conference\'s future. A deal was struck, and in 2001, Anderson’s nonprofit Sapling Foundation acquired TED, and Anderson became its Curator. In taking the conference nonprofit, Anderson stood by the principles that made TED great: the inspired format, the breadth of content, the commitment to seek out the most interesting people on Earth and let them communicate their passion. It soon became clear that the ideas and inspiration generated at TED should have an impact well outside the city limits of Monterey. Accordingly, the years 2001–2006 saw three major additions to the TED family: a sister conference, TEDGlobal, held in locations around the world the TED Prize, which grants its winners one wish to change the world an audio and video podcast series, TED Talks, in which the best TED content is released free online. The first six TED Talks were posted online on June 27, 2006. By September, they had reached more than one million views. TED Talks proved so popular that in 2007, TED\'s website was relaunched around them, giving a global audience free access to some of the world\'s greatest thinkers, leaders and teachers.</string>
    <string name="science_info">The CoEP Science club, nurturing the innovation, raising the profile of science through additional scientific activities has managed to conjure up a lot of interest amongst students of CoEP. Science rules the world; we the mankind just figure it out by making laws and theories. Since birth of mankind he is trying to explain the phenomenon happening in the world with help of science. Integrating technical skill with scientific theories, the club has initiated many projects, some of which being the construction of Microbial Fuel Cell, Project on Special and General Relativity, Quantum Mechanics etc. The club strives to quench a student’s thirst for Science by organizing various exciting events such as Science Quiz’14(a quiz to test people’s knowledge on everything in the field of Science), Talks and Lectures By Eminent Scientists from all over the globe, visits to various labs, workshops and much more. In addition to this, the club is heading towards having a collaboration with Tata Institute for Fundamental Researches (TIFR) and the Inter-University Centre for Astronomy and Astrophysics, Pune (IUCAA), with help of Dr. Yashwant Waghmare. Discussions and brainstorming sessions are also held every week wherein members explore everything under the Sun.</string>
    <string name="science_motto">Science without religion is lame, religion without science is blind</string>
    <string name="science_obj">1. To help students acquire basic knowledge of Science.\n 2. To help students develop a scientific way of learning. \n3. To develop students\' awareness of and concern for scientific issues in personal, social, environmental and technological contexts.\n 4. To arouse and cultivate students\' interest in learning Science.\n 5. To encourage student to participate actively in the activities organized by the Science Club. \n6. To promote the use of IT in learning Science.\n 7. To understand scientific knowledge through experiments.</string>
    <string name="jnvinfo">COEP Janeev Club (previously COEP Environment Club) had evolved from an environmental project initially undertaken by a group of Civil Engineering students. The club realized that all environmental and social issues are interconnected, and do not exist in isolation. Thus, it was decided to transform the club with a view to increase its scope by working on social issues as well. In the year 2011, the Environment Club was transformed into Janeev Club (Marathi: जाणीव, meaning: consciousness) as the socio-environmental club of COEP. The club aims at sensitizing students about various social and environmental issues and enhancing their knowledge regarding the same. The club conducts various activities like lectures and seminars by intellectuals and activists, documentary screenings, classic film screenings, discussions, street plays, awareness campaigns, tree plantation, poetry recitation, etc. Janeev Club members meet every Wednesday at 6 pm in Applied Mechanics Department in front of Boat Club. The club is open to all, runs democratically and disregards any hierarchical structure for its functioning.jnvinfo</string>
    <string name="janvmotto">अंधार भेदणाऱ्या जाणीवांना सामोरे जाऊ या. आपल्या संवेदना जागवू या. पर्यावरणाच्या पलीकडेही डोकावून पाहू या. जागवू या... एक जाणीव!</string>
    <string name="googlemotto">The club aims at conducting events in COEP and on a larger scale at Pune for Google, advocate Google products and technology amongst the mass and represent COEP at Google.</string>
    <string name="googleinfo">Google Student Club, established in 2013 in College Of Engineering Pune is the only Google - affiliated in COEP. Headed by current Google Student Ambassador, selected through a round of tasks, the club aims at bridging the gap between Google and the people who use it by being a mediator.</string>
    <string name="googleach">Google Club has conducted various contests. One of them is Incredible India Photo Shoot. Google+ and the Ministry of Tourism (India) present a photography competition to take the Incredible India campaign to the world and celebrate the visual beauty of India through Google+ Photos. The sole objective of this contest is to capture photo-geniuses from all over the country on to the same G+ platform and showcase and appreciate the beauty of our country. There is also the google cloud developer challenge. Google Cloud Developer Challenge is a contest at international level designed to award the truly deserving developers for creating awesome applications using the Google\'s Cloud Platform. The applications developed should benefit the regions to which the developers belong to. There are 6 regions:India, Sub-Saharan Africa, Middle East and North Africa, South-East Asia, Latin- America, US-Europe and rest of the world.</string>
    <string name="historymotto">To pursue the passion for history</string>
    <string name="historyinfo">The COEP History Club which has ties with Bharat Itihaas Sanshodhak Mandal and Itihaas Premi Mandal, is a social activity pursued by the students of COEP vigorously over last four years out of their passion about history. The club holds regular sessions on various topics such as Troy, Mahabharata, Maratha History, Historic love stories, Joseph Stalin and the likes. The club organizes many site visits and treks to places of historical significance. These tours are guided ones and different field experts or prominent historians are taken along. A \'History Quiz\' was started last year, which received a very good response. History Week is an annual event which comprises of a week-long series of lectures which is attended by people all around Pune. Many well-known personalities in the field of history are invited who enlighten the audience on diverse topics. Students having keen interest in any aspect of history can join the club. No auditions are required.</string>
    <string name="historyach">The History Week is one of the biggest achievements of the club. apart from this there are quizes conducted by the club which are huge success.</string>
    <string name="hammotto">Highlight Amateur Radio and its benefits to countries and communities</string>
    <string name="haminfo">COEP Amateur Radio Club established in 1986 makes itself the oldest technical club of College of Engineering Pune. Starting with vacuum tube transmitters, today the club have gradually upgraded the lab and now it holds advanced transmitters and receivers and other latest equipment. COEP\'s Amateur Radio Club communicates with HAM radio users using the callsign VU2COE. COEP HAM Club provides platform for research in field of Antenna and wireless communication and publish research papers about it.</string>
    <string name="hamach">COEP \'HAM\'s have communicated with almost each and every corner of the world and even with the International Space Station. Every year, HAM Club organizes the A.S.O.C. examination and also coaches students for the same. It also conducts introductory workshops, basic antenna designing workshops annually in COEP and also in other colleges on invitation. The club successfully provides the complete communication link during the various prestigious events of the College of Engineering Pune like Regatta, Mind-spark, Zest, and M.R.A. races held at the COEP Boat Club.</string>
    <string name="dbinfo">The COEP Debate club is Pune’s premier and prestigious debating club which aims towards nurturing debating and public speaking skills of students. It is premiere competitive debating club. It is divided into two sections English and Marathi section. The members participate in various inter college tournaments, viz Parliamentary Debates , Conventional Debates and Model United Nations, in and out of Pune, winning numerous accolades. Being good public speakers , members also play an active role in anchoring college events. The members have regular debating and brainstorming sessions along with workshops for skill refinement.</string>
    <string name="dbach">The Debate Club organises the annual \'Visveswarya Memorial Debate\' and \'CoEP Model United Nations\' through which it promotes discourse in the student community.</string>
    <string name="debatemotto">Spread the poweer of Speech</string>
    <string name="tedxcontact">TedX COEP Head</string>
    <string name="objective">Objective</string>
    <string name="sciencecon">Science Club Head</string>
    <string name="jcon">Janeev Head</string>
    <string name="hiscon">History Club Head</string>
    <string name="spandancon">Spandan Head</string>
    <string name="hamcon">Ham Club Head</string>
    <string name="google_club_head">Google CLub Head</string>
    <string name="dcon">Debate Club Head</string>
    <string name="csatcontact">CSAT Project Manager</string>
    <string name="csatinfo">The COEP Satellite (SWAYAM) project is aimed at developing a reliable bidirectional communications platform.Started in late 2008, the SWAYAM project revolves around the challenge of building a pico-satellite destined to orbit the Earth at a height of 500-800 km.

\n\nWith a total weight of 1 kg and the volume restricted to around 1000 cc, the cube shaped satellite demands an innovative approach at every design phase, from screening of components in order to fit the stringent mass budget to the selection of suitable electronic devices which honour the mere 2 W of power produced by the solar panels. With this in mind, the team has devised an ingenious passive stabilization system which employs a pair of hysteresis rods and a magnet to stabilize the satellite thus eliminating the need to use bulky and power hungry magnetorquers. This Passive Attitude Control System of SWAYAM is the first of its kind in India. The satellite houses a payload capable of half duplex communication over the HAM frequency band which enables it to receive, store and transmit messages from one corner of the globe to the other. The team has also established a functional Ground Station and tracked many amateur radio satellites.

\n\nActing as a platform which enables the students to empirically test their knowledge has always been the corner stone of this project. Right from its inception, the team has been strongly supported by the college on all fronts, providing valuable infrastructure and a strong funding to keep the project alive. The Qualification of the Satellite is ready and has undergone the Environmental test.

\n\nThe team successfully cleared the Critical Design Review (CDR) at ISAC, Bangalore on 17th September 2014. All the subsystem designs and results were presented and approved by the committee. The team got a clearance for going ahead with the Flight Model of Swayam.

\n\nRecently the team completed the Flight Model assembly and Environmental tests on it at ISAC. The Flight Model has been handed over to ISRO and the satellite was launched with Cartosat 2C on 22nd June, 2016. Now the satellite has been launched into the space.

\n\nTeam CSAT has already begun its next project. They are working on a satellite which will demonstrate orbit manoeuvering using solar sails with radiation monitoring as payload.
</string>
    <string name="acmmotto">creating interest among the students in computer science apart from what they learn during the course work.</string>
    <string name="acminfo">ACM is the world’s largest educational and scientific computing society which delivers resources that advance computing as a science and a profession. ACM provides the computing field\'s premier Digital Library and serves its members and the computing profession with leading-edge publications, conferences, and career resources.</string>
    <string name="cofsugmotto">promote the use of Free Software (also known as Open Source Software) in COEP and in other institutions in Pune.</string>
    <string name="cfsinfo">The group runs a mailing list cofsug@googlegroups.com. The group carries out activities like: Installation fests (to teach people how to install GNU/Linux operating system), Workshops on Linux Administration, Drupal, Python, Various FOSS technologies, Creative Commons, Open Hardware and like. The group promotes the development of software with release of code under GNU GPL-v3 license.</string>
    <string name="pdmotto">Strive For Excellence Not Perfection</string>
    <string name="pd_info">The motto of Personality Development Club is to develop character with competence. The club emphasizes on invoking hidden soft skills which are very vital to stay and deal in the current scenario of cut-throat competition. Thus, the club conducts various workshops and training sessions by various experts from the professional world so as to develop communication skills, and to learn about technical presentations and industrial etiquettes.</string>
    <string name="acm_head">ACM Head</string>
    <string name="cofsug_head">CoFSUG Head</string>
    <string name="pdcon">Personality Development Head</string>
    <string name="aarya_raas_head">Aarya Raas Head</string>
    <string name="armotto">Where a Woman\'s Strength is Redefined</string>
    <string name="swf">With the objective of organising and fostering a sense of unity and fraternity amongst students of COEP, in August 1988, the Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar National Association Of Engineers (BANAE) was formed. BANAE is a nationwide organisation registered under the Societies Act, 1960 and Public Trust Act, 1950. Membership of the Association has a wide ranging base; engineers, people from the private sector, professionals and students wings. With the aim of implementing this work of BANAE at college level, STUDENT WELFARE FORUM (SWF), has been established in our college. Under this group we perform various activities such as: 1] Skill development program 2] Youth leadership program 3] Developing awareness amongst students regarding various scholarships 4] Helping financially backward students and scholars 5] Orientation program for first year students 6] Lecture series on various social and educational topics 7] 14 hours continuous study program 8] Mentorship Program 9] Stress management and time management workshops 10] Lectures on MPSC and UPSC 11] Inspirational and motivational lectures.</string>
    <string name="swf_ach">SWF endeavours to bring engineers from various fields together, to work for social welfare. SWF is helpful, especially for those students who come from small towns and rural backgrounds.</string>
    <string name="swf_motto">To serve Humanity is to serve Almighty</string>
    <string name="spic_macay">SPIC MACAY seeks to conserve and promote an awareness of this rich and heterogeneous cultural tapestry amongst the youth of this country through focus on the classical arts, with their attendant legends, rituals, mythology and philosophy and to facilitate an awareness of their deeper and subtler values. The SPIC MACAY is a non-profit, volunteer organization pioneered with the motive to promote Indian classical music, dance, and culture amongst youth. It organizes annual VIRASAT series in which prominent artists perform live and give lecture demonstrations. COEP has a chapter of SPIC MACAY. Music concerts, workshops, film screening, lecture demo are the activities conducted by this club.</string>
    <string name="spic">Music concerts, workshops, film screening, lecture demo are the activities conducted by this club.</string>
    <string name="phylo">Intelligent, ever-motivated, logically sound, witty and a true seeker, is what we engineers pride ourselves to be. But inside each of us, is a small innocent soul, stumbling and learning as it grows up. In this process of growing, each of us develops his/her own philosophy of life. To provide a platform, an outlet to the philosopher inside each of us, the \'Philomystics\' club was started in the college. Throughout the year, the group organizes guest lectures as well as many talks by students, in addition to informal discussions and debates amongst the crowd of enthusiasts! The name Philomystics is a combination of two words - philosophy and mysticism. These two words have a subtle, but important difference between them. It is the difference between talking and thinking all possible ways of crossing a river, and actually crossing it. In this increasingly material-oriented world of ours, there is less and less space for the heart to fly freely. Technology provides us with unimaginable power in hands, but only with a little spiritual nudging, can the power be safely channelized. The group discussions and lectures are free for all interested people, from the college as well as outside. No auditions are required to be given. Anyone interested can freely express his/her own opinions and ideas in the group. Our hopes are that this collective sharing of conscious thoughts can help every seeker walk his path more positively!</string>
    <string name="ecell">The Entrepreneurship Development Cell (more commonly referred to as the ED-Cell) of College of Engineering, Pune was established in 2006. This cell aims to foster the entrepreneurship culture among the students and epitomize the power of innovation. Since its inception,ED-Cell has been primarily responsible for stimulating, sustaining and supporting entrepreneurial endeavors within the campus,providing them with necessary assistance and resources. With dedicated and full-fledged support from Bhau Institute of Entrepreneurship (CoEP), the cell firmly believes in harvesting innovative ideas and intends to nurture them. The club is also associated with National Entrepreneur Network (NEN), who help us build an effective and a vibrant entrepreneurship ecosystem on campus.</string>
    <string name="ecellach">1. Incubation programs \n2. development of entrepreneurship spirit amongst students \n3. paid internship programs</string>
    <string name="edcell">The Entrepreneurship Development Cell (more commonly referred to as the ED-Cell) of College of Engineering, Pune was established in 2006. This cell aims to foster the entrepreneurship culture among the students and epitomize the power of innovation. Since its inception,ED-Cell has been primarily responsible for stimulating, sustaining and supporting entrepreneurial endeavors within the campus,providing them with necessary assistance and resources. With dedicated and full-fledged support from Bhau Institute of Entrepreneurship (CoEP), the cell firmly believes in harvesting innovative ideas and intends to nurture them. The club is also associated with National Entrepreneur Network (NEN), who help us build an effective and a vibrant entrepreneurship ecosystem on campus. Since last 6 years e-fest and e-weekend are organised successfully.</string>
    <string name="i2i"><![CDATA[Ignited Innovators of India Ignited Innovators of India (I2I) is a movement organized by the BHAU institute of Innovation, Entrepreneurship and Leadership [BIEL] at College of Engineering, Pune. I2I is a unique initiative that aspires to reach out to students across India and provide them with an opportunity to become social entrepreneurs and bring about small but significant changes in the world around. The I2I initiative has been instituted with the vision of promoting and instilling entrepreneurship, leadership and team building skills among students in various colleges. The program encourages them to take up innovative projects that hold potential to make a tangible difference to the community. Bhau Institute of Innovation, Entrepreneurship & Leadership at COEP is the backbone of i2i offering students an opportunity to make changes in your world today. I2India Fellows will have the opportunity to network with successful social entrepreneurs, gain leadership and volunteer experiences and work intimately with the local community.]]></string>
    <string name="bhau_ecell_head">Bhau ECell Head</string>
    <string name="mote">Entrepreneurship is an art</string>
    <string name="emo">Entrepreneurship is an art</string>
    <string name="bhau_institute">Bhau Institute</string>
    <string name="phylomystic_head">Phylomystic Head</string>
    <string name="spicmacay_head">Spicmacay Head</string>
    <string name="scontact">SWF Head</string>
    <string name="arainfo">Aarya Raas, a girl\'s club was initiated to promote women empowerment and work for social causes.  When it started in 2007, it was just a small club, self-funded, and dedicated to the spirit of womanhood. We went on growing since then and tried to strengthen the club.   Influencing other people as well, Aarya Raas gets involved in various social activities like visit and support to Old age Homes and Orphanages, organizing free medical checkups and blood donation camps.   Motivating the handicrafts made by women, the women empowerment has also been promoted. It also has been arranging various inspiring lectures and much more.   The most exciting event of Aarya Raas club is \'SHARDIYA NAVARATRI\', which is Successfully Planned, Organized and Executed by Girls. It is the only event of COEP that lasts for longest duration i.e. 9 days. It provides the biggest platform for girls to show their leadership and management qualities.</string>
    <string name="nssmotto">Not me but you</string>
    <string name="nssinfo">The National Service Scheme (NSS) is an Indian government-sponsored public service program conducted by the Department of Youth Affairs and Sports of the Government of India. Popularly known as NSS, the scheme was launched in Gandhiji\'s Centenary year, 1969. Aimed at developing student\'s personality through community service, NSS is a voluntary association of young people in Colleges, Universities and at +2 level working for a campus-community linkage.</string>
    <string name="nss_senior">NSS Senior</string>
    <string name="aim">Aim</string>
    <string name="nssaim">The programme aims to inculcate social welfare in students, and to provide service to society without bias. NSS volunteers work to ensure that everyone who is needy gets help to enhance their standard of living and lead a life of dignity. In doing so, volunteers learn from people in villages how to lead a good life despite a scarcity of resources. it also provides help in natural and man-made disasters by providing food,clothing and first aid to the disaster victims.</string>
    <string name="nsscamp">Annual NSS Camps</string>
    <string name="imsj">Camps are held annually, funded by the government of India, and are usually located in a rural village or a city suburb. \nVolunteers may be involved in such activities as:\n 1.Cleaning \n2.Afforestation \n3.Stage shows or a procession creating awareness of such issues as social problems, education and cleanliness \n4.Awareness Rallies \n5.Inviting doctors for health camps \n\nThere are no predefined or preassigned tasks; it is left up to the volunteers to provide service in any way that is feasible. Camps typically last between a week and 10 days, although camps for shorter periods are also conducted by nss</string>

</resources>
